const storeQuestions = {
  questions: [
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women filed a gender discrimination lawsuit against Kleiner Perkins, was the CEO of Reddit, is an investment partner at Kapor Capital & is a cofounder of the diversity consulting non-profit organization Project Include?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Freada Kapor-Klein",
        "Sheryl Sandberg",
        "Ellen Pao",
        "Mary Meeker"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women challenged Uber on sexism and harrassment in early 2017?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Ingrid Avendano",
        "Susan Fowler",
        "Isis Wenger",
        "Cheryl Y. Sew Hoy"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women led engineering efforts at Google, Slack and sits on the advisory Board for Aptica, Hack the Hood and is a mentor for Black Girls Code?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Erica Baker",
        "Melinda Briana Epler",
        "Yvonne Hutchinson",
        "Aubrey Blanche"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women has over four decades of dedication and experience working at the intersection of racial / social justice and tech & is the Founder / Board Chair at Level Playing Field Institute?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Laura Gomez",
        "Sonja Gittens-Ottley",
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "Freada Kapor Klein"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women started a viral campaign with the hashtag #ilooklikeanengineer in order to promote discussion of gender equality in tech?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Michelle Glauser",
        "Aubrey Blanche",
        "Isis Wenger",
        "Allison Esposito"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women co-founded a $53M Ed-tech fund called Reach Capital, where investments were made in 40+ ed-tech companies, including Schoolzilla, SchoolMint, and Newsela?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Sarah Tavel",
        "Shauntel Poulson",
        "Mary Meeker",
        "Aileen Lee"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women was part of Twitter’s team in it’s early stages responsible for the expansion of Twitter en español, worked at YouTube and is the CEO and founder of Atipica?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Laura Gomez",
        "Mandela SH Dixon",
        "Sonja Gittens-Ottley",
        "Cat Perez"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women is the Founder of Girls Who Code?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Ciara Trinidad",
        "Jennifer Kim",
        "Reshma Saujani",
        "Yvonne Hutchinson"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women leads PyLadiesSF, created the #ILookLikeAnEngineer ad campaign, and founded Techtonica, a tuition-free tech training and job placement program for women and non-binary adults in need?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Michelle Glauser",
        "Angie Chang",
        "Sarah Nahm",
        "Carly Zakin"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which of these badass women was both an investor and Entrepreneur in Residence in the NY office of Comcast Ventures & is a Managing Partner at Core Innovation Capital?",
      questionOptions: [
        "Trae Vassallo",
        "Kat Manalac",
        "Jess Lee",
        "Kathleen Utecht"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3
    }
  ]
};
